A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, John D. Rockefeller, Sr., Series A FA310
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence - Benavedes, E. - Biggar, F. E. (Box 5, Folder 38)
  Benavedes, Ernesto, 1928 - 1929. Mexican, asking for aid.Bender, Caroline E., 1922; 1929. Dimes.Bengis, Abraham, July 11, 1921. Birthday wishes.Benham, Mildred M., January 8, 1925; January 7, 1926. Thanks for gift.Benjamin, L. U., April 4, 1927. Visiting upstate New York.Benjamin, (Mrs.), William M. C., October 4, 1928. Wedding invitation.Bennett, Edwin L., August 1927. Appeal.Bennett, Miss Mozelle, 1920 - 1922. Violinist, played for John D. Rockefeller.Benson, D. P., February 22, 1931. Shook hands.Benson, Emma, July 24, 1929. Thanks for picture.Bent, Lester H., 1927 - 1931. Minister, Pocantico Hills Union Church. Personal gifts. Golf. Visits.Bergstrom, Erik, 1927. Servant, facial affliction.Berrien, Susan M., (Mrs.), April 6, 1925. Visits estate.Berry, C. R. F., February 14, 1930. Sending copper cent.Berry, John F., September 30, 1930. Church appeal.Berry, L. K., 1921. Use of Lakeview Cemetery waste land.Bertron, S. R., October 1921. Suffering in Russian famine.Berwald, G. H., December 1926. Forwarding letter if late J. W. Walton.Bethune, Mary M., (Mrs.), 1927 - 1929. Invitation to Bethune-Cookman College.Bevard, Edna K., April 8, 1929. Enjoy summer.Bevier, Alta L., (Mrs.), 1922 - 1923. New York cousins, Selovers; appeals.Beyer, Richard F., 1924. Thank you.Bickford, Robert S., 1930. Offer of first New York State telephone.Bidwell, Charles, A., 1927. Book request.Biggar, Frederick E. C., May 31, 1930. Wedding invitation.
- Correspondence - Biggar, Hamilton F., 1919-1926 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  Cleveland homeopathic physician. Nickels and dimes. Visits. Gifts. 1921 interview full of errors about John D. Rockefeller. Investments. Deaths.
- Correspondence - Bigger, W. G. - Black, W. (Box 5, Folder 40)
  Biggar, William G., 1927 - 1930. Greene Avenue Baptist Church, Welfkin sermonette; autograph.Billings, Hazel M., September 15, 1920. Bilings, Ray, 1931. Poem read to G. Curci.Bingham, Robert W., January 1928. Editorial on John D. Rockefeller.Bitting, W. C., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1922; 1925; 1926; 1931. Liberal Baptist minister, visits, friendship.Bjorkman, John W., 1921; September 1924. Dimes.Bjornson, Magnhild, 1926. Gift at Christmas.Black, B. B., September 22, 1931. The University of Chicago chapel.Black, J. C. C., Mr. and Mrs. (Anna), 1919 - 1926. Visits, gifts. Atlanta Negro church gift. Death.Black, W. F., August 1, 1922. Friendly sentiments.Black, Witherbee (Mr. and Mrs.) C., June 1927. Wedding invitation.
- Correspondence - Blackler, Mary, 1918-1928 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  Daughter of 1873 Rockefeller coachman. Personal gifts. Friendly letters.
- Correspondence - Blackler, Mary, 1929-1931 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Correspondence - Blagden, L. A. - Boise, Edward (Box 6, Folder 43)
  Blagden, L. A., 1926; 1930. Best wishes. Blair, J. O., (Mrs.), February 25, 1930. Aid for worthy student. Blair, Walter D., (Mrs.), Ethel Gould Blair, 1918 - 1924. Tarrytown Women's Civic League, Christmas tree donations. Blakeman, Lucy, June 1923. Death; John D. Rockefeller pension payments to relative. Blakemore, Delia, 1920. Employee in Cleveland. Furniture storage problems. Blakemore, William C., October 1, 1929. Wedding invitation. Blatchley, W. S., December 1928; January 10, 1929. Send book. Bliss, Cornelius N., May 20, 1927. Church pew. Block, Monroe D., January 9, 1928. Meaning of Kykuit. Blomfield, Jancy, (Mrs.), 1926 - 1927. Captain Walpole Roland. Blood, E. A., July 19, 1929. Thanks for gift. Bloome, Millard J., October 1928. Invitation. Blystone, E. L., 1929. Dimes. Board of Education, Brielle, New Jersey, May 13, 1920. Thanks for spruce tree. Boardman, Florence S., 1920. Washington cathedral. Boardman, Mabel T., June 1920. Request for photograph. Boardman, William T., April - May 1928. Death of Mrs. Boardman. Bohannon, C. C., 1921 - 1923. Specimen analysis - Starr J. Murphy's death. Bohon, C. C., March 1930. Sending photograph, dimes. Boise, Annie V., (Mrs.), 1920 - 1931. John D. Rockefeller gave regularly. Reports on her activities. Boise, Edward, May 3, 1926. Thanks for $50.00.
- Correspondence - Bonitz, F. W. - Brewster, W. J. (Box 6, Folder 44)
  Bonitz, F. W., January 3, 1928. Old Standard Oil employee wants to shake hands.Booise, Irene P., 1930. Aid for relative.Bossom, Emily B., (Mrs.), 1924. Sends book on oil.Bostrom, Charles B., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1921; 1924 - 1925. Florida neighbor, wanted to see John D. Rockefeller land.Bostrom, J. A., March 1925. Condolences.Bostrom, Lars E., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1925; 1927 - 1931. Deaths, dimes, Florida neighbor.Bosworth, Welles, December 11, 1929. Greetings.Bottcher, Wilhelm, October, November 1927. Offers religious sketches.Bouck, Albert T., November 29, 1929. Boys school appeal.Boulware, Aubin L., 1924. Thank you for condolences.Bovard, Walter, (Mr. and Mrs.), December 1931. New Year Card.Bowder, George. June 1923. Visitor.Boes, Edward, July - August 1928. John D. Rockefeller sends radios Major Bowes a photograph.Bowlen, Jean, 1931. John D. Rockefeller picture with child.Bowler, Helen, John D. Rockefeller's niece, Frank's daughter, 1922; 1931. Thanks for gifts.Bowler, Walter S., 1919 - 1931. Cleveland relative.Bowles, Florence E., (Mrs.), July 9, 1930. Questions about his career.Bowles, Lillian I., 1923 - 1931. Thanks for gift.Boy Scouts of America, (Florida and New Jersey), 1929 - 1930. John D. Rockefeller gifts.Boyd, J. Taver (Mr. and Mrs.), March 30, 1931. Dimes.Boyd, W. R., Jr., November 12, 1929. Dimes, visits.Boyer, Gen S., 1924 - 1928. Ormond minister, John D. Rockefeller personal gifts.Brabham, Otis, January 2, 1928. Sending tree root.Bradner, R. Maxwell, April, 1929. Sending poem.Brainard, Henrietta V., 1921. Wedding gift.Braman, Harold P., January 27, 1926. Thanks.Branch, H. C., March 1928. Photograph.Brandon Chamber of Commerce, Vermont, June 14, 1930. Dime for prize.Bratt, Elizabeth I., December 6, 1922. Thanks.Bredin, Walter, July 1928. Declines newsreel appearance.Breed, William C., October 22, 1927. Invitation.Brew, F. C., August 1926. Visitor.Brewster, Benjamin, (Mrs.), April 1925. Condolences.Brewster, Sylvia, 1929. Wedding gift.Brewster, W. J., February 9, 1928. Invitation.
- Correspondence - Briggs, F. F. - Brooks, A. T. (Box 6, Folder 45)
  Briggs, Frederick F., 1920 - 1927. Former employee, best wishes. Brisbane, Arthur, 1927; 1929. Golf Henry Ford, photographs. Broadus, William F., January 1, 1929. Appeal. Brock, Mildred D., August 31, 1927. Dimes. Brooks, Arthur T., 1921 - 1931. Boston minister. Church work. Visits. Personal gifts. Golf. "I Do it Unto Thee" poem.
- Correspondence - Brooks, J. J. - Bruce, J. M. (Box 6, Folder 46)
  Brooks, J. J., April 1929. Poem, "I Do It Unto Thee."Brouillet, A., July 1929. Gift of medicine.Brouwer-Ancher, Edith, December 8, 1927.Brower, A. W., December 13, 1923. John D. Rockefeller's recollection of school days in Cleveland.Brower, Charles E., 1929 - 1931. Remembers early Standard Oil days; praise for Foundation.Brown, Addie V., 1929 - 1931. Old church friend. Personal gifts.Brown, Charles H., November 1920. Golf partner.Brown, Eliza M., June 24, 1926. Visit. Brown, Emma, 1924 - 1931. Personal gifts to DeLap relative in Boston.Brown, Fred, March 25, 1930. Interview declined.Brown, Freeman M., (Mrs.), March 17, 1927. Cleveland history.Brown, Henry C., 1926 - 1927. Lectures on Old New York.Brown, J. Balcolm ( Mr. and Mrs.), April 1928. Wedding invitation.Brown, John C., January 1929. Did John D. Rockefeller know his father.Brown, John T., September 1927. Visit.Brown, Joseph W., April 7, 1930. Met in church, sending pamphlet.Brown, W. R., (Mrs.), April - September 1925. Cleveland Sorosis.Browne, Guy, June 10, 1926. Gifts to church.Browne, Margery, March 1927. Sends drawing.Browne, Mary T., ( Mrs.), 1924 - 1930. John D. Rockefeller sends $5. in dimes each year, missionary work.Brownell Junior High School, Cleveland, 1922; 1924. John D. Rockefeller recalls early education.Broyles, George J., 1929. Dimes.Bruce, Ailsa, May 1926. Wedding invitation (married name, daughter of Secretary of the Treasury).Bruce, James M., 1920. Judson Memorial Church.
- Correspondence - Brush, C. - Burr, H. (Box 6, Folder 47)
  Brush, Charles, June 18, 1929. Death.Brusie, Mary and Eli, 1919 - 1929. Personal gifts to upstate relatives. Alleged scandalous doings.Brusie, Norman, 1930. Appeal from relative.Buchanan, James B., November 23, 1931. Interview.Bucher, A. F., (Mrs.), January 1927. Baby announcement.Bucher, Irene C., May 1925. Church rummage sale.Bueno, Santiago, December 1928 - January 1929. Ship model.Buermann, Robert, August 3, 1925. Photograph received.Bull, Catherine M., August 22, 1925. Wedding gift.Bullock, E. J., January 1930. Photograph.Bullock, Edward W., (Mr. and Mrs.), December 1931. Wedding invitation.Bunting, Christian, September 1, 1931. Buy copies of song, "Story of Love", become famous, religious, dedicated to Bunting.Burchardt, H., (Mrs.), 1920; 1922; 1927; 1929. Birthday wishes.Burchmann, Minnie R., (Mrs.), 1919 - 1926. Alabama cousin. Personal gifts. Personal problem.Burdette, James S., (Mrs.), June 27, 1931. Appeal for aid.Burgwin, William H., December 9, 1930. Dimes.Burke, Charles C., May 1924. Condolence.Burke, Edmund S., (Mr. & Mrs.), October 1930. Wedding invitation.Burke, Josephine, May 1938. Wedding gift.Burkell, Mildred, March 1931. Dimes.Burns, Ella M., July 1924. Reminiscences.Burr, F. M., (Mrs.), December 1924. Condolences.Burr, Henry, April 24, 1931. Health exercises.
- Correspondence - Burr, Josephine, 1920-1927 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  Mrs. Louis H. Burr. Personal gifts. Visits. Wife of minister. Gave John D. Rockefeller dimes to Lindberg.
- Correspondence - Burr, Josephine, 1928-1931 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Correspondence - Burt, F. H. - Buswell, F. L. (Box 7, Folder 50)
  Burt, Frank H., November 14, 1929. John D. Rockefeller visit to Crawford House, New Hampshire, 1865.Burt, O. C., (Mrs.), 1920 - 1926. Personal aid to old Cleveland friend. Her problems.Burton, Grace, February 22, 1928. Appeal.Burton, Margaret E., June 9, 1925. Death of Ernest D. Burton.Busch, A. W., (Mr. and Mrs.), March 14, 1931. Poems.Bushnell, Harriet S., 1922 - 1927. Friendship.Bustard, W. W., 1920 - 1925. Cleveland minister. Death of friends. Church work. John D. Rockefeller paid part of salary. Work of church.Buswell, Fred L., 1921 - 1931. Estate employee. Family gifts.
- Correspondence - Butler, C. P. - Byington, S. B. (Mrs.) (Box 7, Folder 51)
  Butler, Courtlandt P., 1921 - 1931. New Jersey minister. Personal gifts. Visits.Butler, Mother Joseph, July 3, 1922. Invitation.Buttrick, Wallace, 1921; 1926. Birthday wishes; deathByers, Vincent G., April 1928. PhotographByington, Sallie B., (Mrs.), January 1926. Church appeal.
- Correspondence - C., Evelyn - Cary, M. F. (Box 7, Folder 52)
  C., Evelyn, 1929. Golf game.Caddagan, D. C., 1927. Invitation to join club.Cadman, S. Parkes, 1924 - 1926. Thanks for praise.Caley, Fred H., February 1927. Thanks for good works.Call, Bessie H., January 16, 1929. Visit.Callmayer, Marie L., February 10, 1930. Golf, photos.Calloway, Alfred W. (Mr. and Mrs. and Family), 1921 - 1930. Businessman, Visits. Davis Coal & Coke.Calvert, John, March 23, 1927. Appeal, (Chicago).Calvert, John, April 9, 1929. Poem, (Philadelphia).Calvert, Mary, July 1928. Death of William Calvert.Cammack, J. W., February 1927. Invitation.Campbell, Fannie, 1920 - 1922. Cleveland friend. Christmas gifts.Canning, W. R., January - February 1929. Apples.Cannon, Katherine, 1920. Financial help; death expenses.Capri, Peter, May - June 1931. John D. Rockefeller poem set to music.Carder, Eugene C., March 5, 1928. Death of Dr. Woelfkin.Carey, Martin, 1922. Death.Cariss, Walter L., May 12, 1927. Dime.Carlson, August - January 7, 1921. Thanks for chestnut.Carnegie, Nancy, 1925. Wedding gift (married James Stillman Rockefeller).Carnell, Johnnie G., (Mrs. D. P.), January 4, 1922. Gift.Carnell, Stanley M., April 1923. Stick to the church.Carner, Addie, September 19, 1931. Ran tourist home where John D. Rockefeller stayed.Carpenter, Harriett, (Mrs.), July 1920. Visitor.Carpenter, Helen C., 1920 - 1930. Visits. Gifts.Carpenter, J. J., November 1931. Gift of shell tray returned.Carroll, Charles, December 1925. Likes marble image at 26 Broadway.Carruthers, Sarah C., (Mrs.), January 1926. Appeal.Carter, Garnet, October - November 1928. Sends miniature golf course.Carter, Marcellus E., August 1929. Employee complaint.Cartier, Inc., December 2, 1931. Delivery announcement.Carwile, Z. W., July 1921. Birthday wishes.Cary, Edward V., (Miss Miriam), 1920; 1927 - 1930. Office employee. Personal gifts. Best wishes.Cary, Mary F., February 27, 1924. Gift.
- Correspondence - Case, W. B. - Cawley, E. D. (Box 7, Folder 53)
  Case, William B., May 1931. Appeal.Casselman, Francis R., August 24, 1928. Personal gift.Casterton, J. Ward, June 1929. Condolence.Castner, Charlotte C., 1921. Visit.Catholic (Colored) Church Cleveland, 1923. John D. Rockefeller gives $2250. to buy an organ for Church of Our Lady of the Blessed Sacrament.Cauldwell, Caroline J., (Mrs.), 1919 - 1931. Visits. Suffragette. Birthday wishes, (also with Dr. Charles Cauldwell).Cavling, Ole, January - February 1930. Autographed picture.Cawein, Kathrine, July 18, 1929. Visit.Cawley, Eleazer D., August 4, 1930. Appeal.
- Correspondence - Cecil, J. S. - Cheetham, T. L. (Mrs.) (Box 7, Folder 54)
  Cecil, J. S., March - April 1926. Appeal.Central High School, Cleveland, 1920 - 1921; 1928; 1930. Special message. Diamond reunion. John D. Rockefeller recollections.Chadwick, E., (Mrs.), September 1926. Help for daughter.Chapin, F. M., 1928. Seasons Greetings.Chapin, Sallie, February 9, 1920. Birthday wishes.Chapin, William W., (Mr. and Mrs.), October 1926. Anniversary wishes.Chaplain, Charles H., 1928. Organist out of work.Chapman, Alson, August 1, 1931. Claims pay earned in 1879.Chapman, Fannie, (Mrs.), 1920 -1923. Visits.Chapman, Frank C., 1923. Barnard statues.Chapman, L. O., October 19, 1923. Appeal.Chapman, W. S., (Mrs.), January 16, 1931. Photo.Chappel, Zenobia D., June 1931. Davison genealogy.Chapple, Joe M., 1920 - 1925; 1930 -1931. Visits, poem.Chard, Mary H., January 10, 1930. Greetings.Chard, Mr. and Mrs. Thourton, C., September 1927. Wedding invitation.Chase, Fannie D., (Mrs.), November - December 1920. List of non-smokers.Chase, Harry, November - December 1929. Visit.Chase, Henry J., February 1923. Appeal.Chase, L. Vernon, 1921 - 1931. Gifts. News on upstate relatives.Chase, Phoebe T., (Mrs.), 1921; 1927. Dime.Cheetham, Thomas L., October 9, 1929. Visit.
- Correspondence - Cheney, James L. and Family, 1919-1931 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  Minister, Cleveland. Personal gifts. Church work. Retirement. Pension by John D. Rockefeller.
- Correspondence - Chenoweth, A. K. - Cleveland Chamber of Commerce (Box 8, Folder 56)
  Chenoweth, Austin K., July 1926. Birthday wishes.Cherdron, O. P., April 1929. Sends speech.Chester, C. M., February - March 1929. Comments on oil business.Chisholm, Alvah S., (Mrs.), February 1929. Wedding invitation.Chisholm, Bruce, October 1921. Wedding invitation.Chisholm, Mary. Appeal on behalf of old friend.Chisholm, Stewart H., 1927; 1930. Dime, birthday wishes, church work.Chisholm, Willson B., (Mrs.), 1922. Appeal for memorial to women.Chivers, E. E., (Mrs.), 1917. Personal gift.Chon, Ben W., July 1927. Visit.Christensen, Christian (Mr. and Mrs.), 1928. Personal gift.Christiancy, Patty, (Mrs.), April - May 1930. Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) appeal.Ciampi, John, 1929. Reference letter.Ciampi, Rocco, 1923; 1924; 1929 - 1930. New Jersey employee. Personal gifts.Clark, A. Bayard, May 1927. Offers a General Grant letter.Clark, Ambrose R., 1924 - 1925. Young Men's Bible Class, Church memoirs.Clark, David C., (Mrs.), January - February 1930. Good wishes.Clark, Frank A., April 21, 1930. Orphans.Clark, John, February 1927. Golf tees.Clark, Julia Kempshall, (Mrs.), April 4, 1921. Best wishes.Clark, L. E., (Mrs.), February 14, 1924. Daughter-in-law of early John D. Rockefeller partner, Richard Clark. Appeal for aid.Clark, Noah F., (Mrs.), March - April 1928. Death of Mr. Clark.Clark, N. Norton, January 14, 1931. Visit.Clark, Percy H., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1930. Nelson A. Rockefeller father-in-law, visit to Florida.Clark, William W., 1920 - 1922. Visit.Clarke, Margaret, 1927. Happy birthday.Clarke, Martha A., January 1923. Gift.Clarke, School of the Deaf, Northampton, February 22, 1929. Re: Coolidge Fund.Clear, John, December 14, 1925. Death of Mrs. Clear & Mr. Clear.Cleland, C. S., July 1927. Possible Spelman pictures.Clemmons, Ella May, August 25, 1931. Sends John D. Rockefeller dime.Cleveland, Frances E., (Mrs. Livingston W.), 1921 - 1923. Visit, dime.Cleveland, Pearl (Mrs.), January 30, 1931. Upstate relative appeal.Cleveland Baptist Church Association, 1923; 1928 - 1930. Church appeals. John D. Rockefeller dime put in cornerstone of Broadview Baptist Church.Cleveland Chamber of Commerce, 1923; 1928. Anniversary greetings.
- Correspondence - Clinger, A. G. - Collier, B. G. (Box 8, Folder 57)
  Clinger, Avery G., November 1925. Sends book.Clovernook, February 24, 1930. Sends poem in Braille.Cobb, Dorothy H., September 13, 1931. Death of mother.Cocks, Mary A., (Mrs. Edmund), January 19, 1929. Sends book.Code, T. A., April 23, 1930. Picture.Cody, Mary F., August 1920. Would rent Strong cottage.Coffin, John R., October 1926. Wedding invitation.Coffin, Antoinette (Mrs. Walter E.), 1920; 1931. Cleveland neighbor, troubles, condolences.Cohan, Harold, July 28, 1927. Thanks for nickels for boys of Hebrew Sheltering Guardian Society of New York.Cohn, Alfred E., April 25, 1927. Results of medical examination.Colby, Betty, 1920.Colby, Miss Edith, September 1927. Wedding present.Colby, Everett, (Mr. and Mrs.), December 1929. Wedding invitation.Colby, Whitney C., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1920; 1922; 1926. Standard Oil employee, personal gifts.Cole, Alfred B., (Mrs.), December 30, 1928. Christmas wishes.Cole, Howard E., 1922; 1930. Standard Oil employee, picture.Coleman, Charles, Jr., (Mrs.), August 1928. Appeal.Coleman, H. H., (On his behalf from Eliza Etzenspenger), February 1931. Interview.Coles, Francis W., August 1921. Estate entry permission.Colgate, G. C., January 11, 1930. Gifts to Riverside Church.Colgate, James C., 1920 - 1922. Gifts to Colgate University, Riverside Church.Colgate, Rochester Divinity School, October 1929. Invitation.Colgate University Alumni, 1924. Dollar campaign.Collet, H., January 25, 1929. Dime, archery.Collier, Barron G., (Mr. and Mrs.), 1921 - 1931. Pocantico neighbor, Golf. Gifts.
- Correspondence - Collier, N. W. - Coombe, Edith C. (Box 8, Folder 58)
  Collier, Nathan W., August 1, 1921. Death of C. T. Walker.Collier Institute, June 12, 1930. Invitation.Collings, G. E., September 1926. The horse "Midnight".Collins, Charles A., (Mr. and Mrs.), June 1930. Wedding invitation.Collins, Gertrude E., January 6, 1924. Visit, Florida, Golf.Collis, Charles, February 1, 1924. Visit, picture.Collis, U. G., May 31, 1927. Urge John D. Rockefeller protest lobbying attempt in Florida affecting Ohmard.Colter, Mary E., March 1929. J. D. Archbold's sister. Congratulations on John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s victory over Stewart.Colton, William N., September 19, 1930. Thanks for flowers.Columbia Association of Baptist Churches, May 1, 1928. Thanks for gifts.Columbia University, July 1928. Invitation.Combs, A. H., October 15, 1921. Request recommendation.Comey, J. F., January, June 1922. Photograph, condolence.Commiskey, Mrs. George, October 8, 1929. Relationship claimed, visit requested.Commiskey, Helen A., May 15, 1925. Relationship claimed, visit requested.Community Chest of the Tarrytown, September 1920. Contribution.Compton, John C., March 22, 1930. Dime.Concannon, John, (Mrs.), August 19, 1925. Death of husband.Condon, Joseph J., August - September 1925. Recommendation declined.Conklin, W. R., September 18, 1930. Photograph.Connor, Jeanette T., February 8, 1926. Florida State Historical Society.Connor, Washington E., December 1922 - January 1923. Information on Spanish missions in Florida.Conover, Voorhis C., October 19, 1921. Trip to California.Conrad, L. I., March 6, 1931. Tradesman.Conroy, Elizabeth D., (Mrs.), September 21, 1930. Appeal.Conwell, Russell H., 1920. Gift.Cook, Ellenor, February - March 1927. Invitation.Cook, Joseph, February 23, 1931. Condolence.Cook, Lewis K., November 1928. History of Ohio Canal.Cook, Mary S., 1919 - 1921; 1927. Friendly letters; Sister of Kate Strong.Cook, Ruby, (Mrs.), October 27, 1931. Relative claim.Coolidge, Calvin, 1923 - 1930. Greetings and condolences.Coombe, A. Palmer, 1920 - 1928. President, Standard Oil of Ohio. Golf. Visits. Resignation.Coombe, Edith C., 1923.
- Correspondence - Cooper, H. E. - Cunningham, A. M. (Box 8, Folder 59)
  Cooper, Henry E., July 7, 1931. Birthday wishes.Corey, Winifred E., May, 1925. Visit.Cornell, Betty, January 13, 1930. Gift.Cornell, Carleton, September 20, 1929. Gift.Cornell, Elizabeth Swift, January 8, 1930. Wedding gift.Corney, J. F., August 3, 1921. Sends health program, (simple exercise for the relief of constipation).Corradinni, Antonio, January - February, 1930. Sends sketch.Correll, L., October 7, 1926. Church appeal, Lakewood.Corss, Charles, (Mrs.), April 5, 1928. Dime.Cory, Helen M., April 15, 1931. Appeal.Coutant, Grace, (Mrs.), 1921 - 1930. Doctors in Tarrytown, personal appeal.Coutant, R. B.Covert, Alice, (Mrs.), 1920 - 1924. Personal gifts.Covert, Mary A.Covington, L. J., October 6, 1930. Personal gifts.Cowan, William C., October 1922. Death and estate.Cowen, Edward C., June - July 1926. Wants family information.Cox, Coleman, November - December 1931. Sends book.Cragin, Charles I., (Mrs.), May - June 1924. Asks name of architect of Union Church, P.H.Craig, Edith G., August 12, 1926. Wants to meet John D. Rockefeller.Craig, William S., (Mrs.), August 17, 1926. African missionary. Report on work, (with photo).Crandall, H. I., April 1924. Alleged relation.Crane, Edwin A., February 18, 1930. Thanks for motion picture film.Crane, William M., December 17, 1921. Visit.Crawford, Charles, December 8, 1922. History of lumbering in Huron County, Michigan, Oblique appeal, (with photos).Creekmore, C. B., (Mrs.), and Campbell, Henry, (Mrs.), Hickok, H. W., (Mrs.), and Jones, Minnie, April - May 1927. Sends gift, Tulsa, OK.Crile, George W., (Dr. & Mrs.), May 1922. Wedding invitation.Critchley, Peter, 1926 - 1929. Job for son, Christmas gift Pocantico.Cromaine Society, April - June 1926. Photograph requested.Crone, Thomas E., October 17, 1920. New boiler for house.Crossley, Walter S., May 1929. Appointment.Crozier, Clara, (Mrs.), 1921 - 1923. Relative, gift.Cummings, Damon E., August 30, 1930. Visit.Cummings, Rev. Thomas J. B., 1920 - 1930. Catholic priest, Pocantico Hills, Gifts.Cunningham, A. Marie, August - September 1928. Dime.
- Correspondence - Cuppy, Hazutt A., 1918-1931 (Box 8, Folder 60)
  Loans. Cuppy's financial career. Chocolate business. Law suit. Golf. University of Chicago man.
- Correspondence - Curran Campaign - Cuykendall, W. D. (Mrs.) (Box 8, Folder 61)
  Curran Campaign, October - November 1921. John D. Rockefeller contribution to New York mayoralty primary.Curry, Sara, November 13, 1926. Gift to day nursery.Curtis, Cierro B., (Mrs.), and Anne Donohue, 1919 - 1921. Gifts. Death.Curtis, Mattoon M., 1924 - 1931. Gifts of flowers.Cushing, John J., March 1931. Book of poems.Cuthbert, Frederick T., 1927 - 1928. Visit; death of wife.Cutler, Bertram, 1923 - 1929. Investments. Wedding.Cutler, Robert, 1926. Dinner.Cuykendall, Emma Everson (Mrs. W. D.), 1920 - 1921; 1926. Moravia, New York visits.
- Correspondence - Dailey, C. N. (Mrs.) - Davey, M. L. (Box 8, Folder 62)